const javaQuestion =[
      {
           question: "Number of primitive data types in Java are? ",
           option: [ " 6", " 7"," 8"," 8" ],
           ans: 4
      },

      {
          question: "To which of the following does the class string belong to. ",
          option: ["java.lang"," java.awt"," java.applet"," java.string" ],
          ans: 1
      },

      {
        question: "Total constructor string class have? ",
        option: ["3","7","13","20" ],
        ans: 3 
      },

      {
        question: "  Where does the system stores parameters and local variables whenever a method is invoked? ",
        option: ["Heap","Stack","Array ", " Tree", ],
        ans: 2
      },

      {
        question: "What is the implicit return type of constructor?  ",
        option: [ "No return type"," Aclass object in which it is defined", " Void", " None"],
        ans:2
      },

      {
        question: "Exception created by try block is caught in which block ", 
        option: ["catch"," throw", "final", " none" ],
        ans: 1
      },

      {
        question: "  Which of the following exception is thrown when divided by zero statement is executed?",
        option: ["NullPointrException"," NumberFormatException"," ArithmaticExceotion"," None", ],
        ans: 3
      },

      {
        question: "  Where is System class defined? ",
        option: [ "java.lang.package"," java.util.package"," java.io.package","None" ],
        ans: 1
      },

      {
        question: "  Identify the interface which is used to declare core methods in java ",
        option: [" Comparator", " EventListener", " Set", " Collection"],
        ans: 4, 
      },

      {
        question: "  Which of the following is used to find and fix bugs in the program? ",
        option: ["JDK", " JRE"," JVM"," JDB" ],
        ans: 4
      },
      
    ]; 
   
    
